

SKILLS

Programming

Python · Django · JavaScript · Html · Css ·

Deployment · C · DRF

Data Skills

MySQL · Postgresql

Deployment

Heroku · Railway · Linode

TRAINING/COURSES

CS50's Introduction to Computer Science

Harvard, Completed

CS50's Introduction to Programing with Python. Harvard, Completed

riai vara, completed

CS50's Web Programming with Python and JavaScript

Harvard, Running

STRENGTHS

Quick Learner

Learning new skills, technologies, and roles comes naturally to me.

Problem Solver

In CS50's courses there were so many problems that I have solved on my own. Also I have developed logics and models by making web app assignments.

Effective Communicator

Communication has played an essential part in working in Banking sector and collaborating with my team.

Accountability

I take ownership of my mistakes so that I learn what I did wrong.

MD MOINUDDIN HASAN CHOWDHURY

Entry Level Backend Developer

- \$\ +8801720972766 @ raihaniub587@gmail.com
- https://github.com/moinuddin587
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohammad-moinuddin-hasan-chowdhury-45ab1b25b/

SUMMARY

Entry level Python developer with a strong background of experience in banking sector. Aiming to develop my skills and become a Python Developer at first. Willing to be work in any stack or technology in future. Very passionate and interested to work with any organization and learn something new.

EDUCATION

M.B.A in Finance and Banking

2015 - 2016

Independent University, Bangladesh

Bashundhara R/A,Dhaka

GPA 3.63 / 4.0

PROJECTS

Commerce

A Django-based eBay-like e-commerce auction site.

Functionalities: Creating models for auction listings, bids, and comments, views active listings, add items to their watchlist, browse categories.

To watch video presentation of the project, click here https://youtu.be/HBYzOvI5sRc To know more about project, please visit -

https://github.com/moinuddin587/Commerce

EXPERIENCE

Officer(General Banking)

2019 - 2021

Al Arafah Islami Bank Ltd

Mohakhali Br., Dhaka

Area of Expertise

General Banking (2.7 yrs)

Retail Business Associates

2018 - 2019

The Premier Bank Ltd Head Office

Banani(HO), Dhaka

Area of Expertise CRM (1.2 yrs), General Banking (1.2 yrs), Retail Banking (1.2 yrs) Duties/Responsibilities Working as a CRM support Executive

Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?